// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "The capital of Iran is:",
    answer: "Tehran",
    options: [
      "Kabul",
      "Tehran",
      "Zahedan", 
      "Taftan", 
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "The Shrine of Khawaja Ghulam Farid(R.H) is located in:",
    answer: "Rajanpur",
    options: [
      "Ranikot",
      "Rajanpur",
      "Ranipur",
      "Rawalkot",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question:  "Arabic is not a official language of:",
    answer: "Turkey",
    options: [
      "Kuwait", 
      "Qatar", 
      "Bahrain", 
      "Turkey",
      
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Who authored 'Long Walk of Freedom':",
    answer: "Nelson Mandela",
    options: [
      "Karl Marks", 
      "Jawaharial Nehru", 
      "Nelson Mandela",
      "Barack Hussein Obama", 
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which of the following landlocked sea?",
    answer: "Aral Sea",
    options: [
      "Arabian sea", 
      "South China Sea", 
      "Aral Sea",
      "Yellow Sea", 
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which of the following languages has most alphabets?",
    answer: "Sindhi",
    options: [
      "Urdu", 
      "Sindhi",
      "English", 
      "Balochi", 
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Tibet is an autonomous region of:",
    answer: "China",
    options: [
      "India", 
      "Russia", 
      "China",
      "Nepal", 
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Official Currency of Yemen is:",
    answer: "Rial",
    options: [
      "Rial", 
      "Dirham", 
      "Dinar",
      "Ringgit", 
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "+92 is the country code of:",
    answer: "Pakistan",
    options: [
      "Saudi Arabia", 
      "China", 
      "Pakistan",
      "Kuwait", 
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Tomb of Babur the First Mughal emperor is in:",
    answer: "Kabul",
    options: [
      "Tashkent", 
      "Bukhara", 
      "Kabul",
      "Peshawar", 
    ]
  },
    
    {
    numb: 11,
    question: "National Flower of Pakistan is:",
    answer: "Jasmine",
    options: [
      "Rose", 
      "Tulip", 
      "Jasmine",
      "Lily", 
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 12,
    question: "The Secretary General of the OIC is elected for the period of:",
    answer: "5 Years",
    options: [
      "3 Years", 
      "4 Years", 
      "5 Years",
      "6 Years", 
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 13,
    question: "Which of the following uses GMT+5 as its standard time?",
    answer: "Pakistan",
    options: [
      "Bangladesh", 
      "India", 
      "Pakistan",
      "Afghanistan", 
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 14,
    question: "The Land of Kangaroo:",
    answer: "Australia",
    options: [
      "Brazil", 
      "Australia", 
      "South Africa",
      "Thailand", 
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 15,
    question: "Which country won ICC Women's Cricket World Cup 2022",
    answer: "Australia",
    options: [
      "India", 
      "England", 
      "Australia",
      "South Africa", 
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];
